My name is Jordan Hart, and I'm from Essex.
So it broke us for me to have a really big weight loss journey.
I've lost almost 17 stone myself in two and a half years
with the aid of everyone here at Blueprint.
That is the consistency of coming three to four times a week
to small group, but also other services that I offer.
So Metcon classes, sweat classes, boxing classes.
I've just been in a real community gym
where I feel ultra, ultra comfortable to come here.
It's not a scary, pasty car.
It's coaches and people here that become friends.
And it's not only the gym setting,
it's also the white setting.
So, you know, going out as a group outside the gym,
going to the golf together, whatever it may be,
it just makes you feel really welcome.
And that old evening gives you the confidence to come.
You're never in fear of,
oh my gosh, I need to go to the gym,
but I don't know the person, or I'm afraid,
whatever it be, because it can be quite a scary setting.
And this is complete, complete of set up.